Guide to the William L. Mertz transportation collection, 1955-1990
George Mason University Libraries
- William L. Mertz transportation collection
  - Federal Aid Highway Act, Senate 5/56-6/56 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Interstate Design Policy 1944-1948 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Highway Survey Papers 1915-1979 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Highway Planning Technical Report, Coordinated Data System for Highway Planning 5/68 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Highway Planning Technical Report, License Plate Traffic Survey 5/68 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Highway Planning Technical Report, Monte Carlo Simulation for Origin-Destination Surveys 7/68 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Highway Planning Technical Report, A Mail Survey to Collect Truck Commodity Data 4/69 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Highway Planning Technical Report,Application of Automated Vehicle Registration Files to Postal O-D Surveys 4/69 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Highway Planning Technical Report, Determination of needed Rest Area Comfort Facilities by Systems Analysis 4/69 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Highway Planning Technical Report, Evaluation of Bias in License Plate Traffic Survey Response 7/69 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Highway Planning Technical Report, Summary of the 1968 National Rest Area Usage Study 7/69 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Highway Planning Technical Report, Weekend Recreational Travel Patterns 2/71 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Highway Planning Technical Report, Review of Urban Goods Movement Studies 4/71 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Highway Planning Technical Report, A Grouping Procedure 3/71 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Highway Planning Technical Report, Summary of the 1969 National Rest Area Usage Study and the 1970 Update of the Rest Area Inventory 5/71 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Highway Planning Technical Report, Sampling Surveys for Estimating Local, Rural and Urban Vehicle Miles of Travel 7/73 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Highway Planning Technical Report, Urban Transportation Planning and Air Quality 4/74 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Highway Planning Technical Report, The Texas Procedure for Weighing Trucks in Motion 5/74 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Benefits of Interstate Highways 6/70 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Highway Travel Trends during the 1970's 7/80 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Rest Area Use Study Manual 5/69 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Recording and Coding Guide for the Structure inventory and Appraisal of the nations Bridges 4/71 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Truck Traffic Volume and Weight Data for 1971 and Their Evaluation 12/76 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Manuscript: Origins of the Interstate by Mertz 12/18/86 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Manuscript: Origins of the Interstate by Mertz 12/18/86 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Background papers for Origins of the Interstate by Mertz (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - Altimeter # 112 - Lincoln Highway (Box 17)
    Optical instrument - unknown use
  - 1990 nationwide Personal Transportation Study 8/91 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - the 1991 status of the Nation's Highways and Bridges; Early Results 7/2/91 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - The 1991 status of the Nation's Highways and Bridges 11/91 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - America on the Move! The Story of the Federal Aid Highway Program and the Federal-State Relationship 1977 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - America on the Move! The Story of the Federal Aid Highway Program 9/84 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - America's Challenge for Highway Transportation in the 21st Century: Interim Report of the Future National Highway Program Task Force. 11/88 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - American Association of Highway Officials 50th Anniversary: a Story of the Beginning, Purposes, Growth, Activities and Achievements of AASHO 1965 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - American Trucking Trends Edition 1991-92 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Assessing the Relationship Between Transportation Infrastructure and Productivity 8/92 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Electronic Computer Program for Assignment of Traffic to Street and Freeway Systems (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Beyond Gridlock: The Future of Mobility as the Public Sees It "inclusive">6/88 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Backsights [history of Virginia roads] 1985 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Basic Directions for a New Surface Transportation Program Summer 1989 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Benchmark Survey: Park and Ride Station and service at New Brunswick, New Jersey on Penn Railroad 6/63 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - A Future Highway Program for America: Proposals to be discussed at the Highway Users' Congress on Transportation Futures 9/19/88 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - CAFE or Price? An Analysis of the effects of Federal Fuel Economy regulations and gasoline Price on New Car MPG, 1978-1989 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Case Studies of the Link Between Transportation and Economic Productivity 9/4/90 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - The Changing Harbor front [New York/New Jersey]:a report of prospects for new development of released lands 3/66 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Commuting in America: A National Report on Commuting Patterns and Trends [fall of 1986] (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Comparative Performance of State highway Systems 1984-1989 January 1991 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - Comparing Transport Energy Consumption by mode and Settlement Patterns [UK] [1991] (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - Coordinated Bus-Rail Service: Rockland County-Westchester County-New York City 3/64 (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - Cost Effectiveness of Future Fuel Economy Improvements [1987] (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - Cost of Owning and Operating Automobiles, Vans and Light Trucks 1991 4/92 (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - Tri-State Commission[NJ,NY,CN] Regional Profile Daily Vehicular Travel 2/67 (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - Designs for Growth: A Report on the Tri-State[NJ,NY,CN] Transportation Committee 1961-1966 5/67 (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - Energy from Fossil Fuels 9/90 (Box 18, Folder 27)
  - Public Roads A Journal of Highway research 10/58 (Box 18, Folder 28)
  - An Evaluation of Urban Transportation Planning 2/71 (Box 18, Folder 29)
  - Exploring Key Issues in Public-Private Partnerships for Highway Development 6/92 (Box 18, Folder 30)
  - External travel Survey; Interviewing Procedure Manual 9/62 (Box 18, Folder 31)
  - Tri-State [NY,NJ,CN] Transportation Committee Facts 4/64 (Box 18, Folder 32)
  - Final Report on the Federal Highway Cost Allocation Study 5/82 (Box 18, Folder 33)
  - Financing Federal-Aid Highways - An Implication 7/74 (Box 18, Folder 34)
  - Regional Profile Floor Space and Travel 11/66 (Box 18, Folder 35)
  - Electronic Computer Program for Forecasting Interzonal Traffic movements (Fratar Method) (Box 18, Folder 36)
  - Regional Profile Freight Traffic [1964] (Box 18, Folder 37)
  - Regional Profile Freight Traffic 6/66 (Box 18, Folder 38)
  - General Aviation: Airports for the Future 3/65 (Box 18, Folder 40)
  - General Aviation:Economics of Public-use Airports in the Tri-State Region 7/65 (Box 18, Folder 41)
  - General Aviation: Inventory of Public-use Airports in the Tri-State Region 5/65 (Box 18, Folder 42)
  - General Aviation: The nations Business Aircraft Fleet 8/65 (Box 18, Folder 43)
  - The Atlanta Success Story 1991 (Box 18, Folder 44)
  - Correspondence to John Maloney Regarding History of Bureau of Roads and Thomas H. MacDonald (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - The History and Development of Road Building in the United States 10/6/26 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Notes on Speech by Fairbanks re:Road Surveys 7/23/38 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - History of Road Building Including Time Line of Roads BC (Box 19)
  - Statement of Early Developments Relating to Traffic Signs 3/65 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - General Works of Reference on the History of Road making 300-1840 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Memorandum Concerning an Administration Highway Policy 11/15/38 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Automobile Costs 4/12/38 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - History of Public Roads Administration Participation in the War Effort [ WW I and II ] (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Index to G.A.M.'s and Similar Memorandum 2/1/54 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - the Interstate Highway System: Historical Development [1939-1957] (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Analysis of David Brinley's Television Program of 10/1/62; the Great Highway Robbery 10/62 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Research and the Engineer 12/3/64 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Trends in Highway Taxation in the United States 5/6-18/63 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - The Effect of Modern Highway and of Airline Service on Urban Manufacturing Growth 7/16/68 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Interim Report - Interests System Study of Development as of March 31, 1986 6/9/86 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence from Edwin W. James regarding History of Federal Aid Roads 3/1/67 [2/21/67] (Box 19, Folder 17)
    2 hand written letters from Mr.James quoted in a inclusive document
  - News Releases and Internal Memos Regarding Funding and Progress of the Interstate Highway System 1/1/85 - 6/25/86 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Interstate System 1000 Mile Addition Index of Proposed Urban Routes September 1956 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Appendix B [maps of urban areas] of a Study of the Best Technical Utilization of Additional 1,000 Miles, Authorized by Federal - Highway Act of 1956 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Appendix B [maps of urban areas] of a Study of the Best Technical Utilization of Additional 1,000 Miles, Authorized by Federal - Highway Act of 1956 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Pentagon Study [correspondence regarding the study of traffic needs for Shirley Highway] 1961 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Pentagon Study [correspondence regarding the study of traffic needs for Shirley Highway] 1960 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Shirley Highway - Bus Lanes 1972 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Pentagon area Transportation, Study Appendix H, Vehicle classification and car Occupancy 9/1/60 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Reports Distributed on Pentagon Area Transportation Study [Shirley Highway] 9/62 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - AASHTO Monthly Journal 3/74 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Abstracts from American Highways 1/73 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Abstracts from American Highways 1969 - 1972 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Abstracts from American Highways 1969 - 1972 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Abstracts from American Highways 1965 -1968 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Abstracts from American Highways 1961 - 1964 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Abstracts from American Highways 1957- 1960 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - The "3c" Planning Process [Congressional hearings on urban portions of the Interstate Highway system, specific emphasis on D.C.] 6/25-27/63 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Building the Interstate [history from 1956 to 1962] (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Building the Interstate [history from 1962 to 1973] (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - [House] Hearings on the 1962 Highway Act 1/2/87 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - American Highways 1957 -1960 12/16/86 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - News Clips 1962 - 1963 1/2/87 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Abstracts Thomas H MacDonald 1932 - 1934 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Abstracts of Thos. MacDonald speeches 1935-1941 HRB (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Miscellaneous Abstracts and Compilations by Mertz (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Abstracts Thos H MacDonald (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Moving America: New Directions, New Opportunities [ A Statement of National transportation Policy] 2/8/90 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - A nation in Motion: Historic American Transportation Sites 8/76 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - The Nations Public Works: Defining the Issues [report to President and Congress] 9/86 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - National Air Quality and emissions Trend Report 1990 11/91 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - New haven Railroad Commuter Service: A Mass Transportation Grant Project 12/65 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - New Perspectives in Commuting 7/92 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - New transportation Concepts for a New Century 10/89 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - North American Standard Commercial Vehicle Inspection Guide (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - The Organization and Management of the Department of Transportation 3/91 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Tri State Transportation Committee: Organization: Data Processing, Travel Analysis, Data Collection 3/63 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Park 'n Rail Service; New Brunswick-Newark-New York City 4/65 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Park 'n Rail Service; New Brunswick-Newark-New York City 1/65 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Park N' Rail Service; New Brunswick, Jersey Avenue Station 5/67 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Pavement and Bridge Impacts of Longer Combination Vehicles 6/30/90 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Penn Station [NYC] Traffic Potential East and West 9/66 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Pennsylvania Turnpike: A History 1990 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Public Transport Services to Non-CBD [Central Business District] Employment Concentrations 9/67 and amp 1/69 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Tri-State Transportation Commission Regional Profile: Personal Income and Consumption Expenditures 7/67 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - A Plan for "Commuting in America" (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - Population, Economic, and Land Use studies in Urban Transportation Planning 7/64 (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - Productivity and Consumer Benefits of Longer Combination Vehicles 5/14/90 (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - Prosecutes for Tri-State Transportation Committee 4/62 (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - Public and Private Sector Roles in Intelligent Vehicle - Systems [IVHS] Deployment 8/92 (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - Rail Freight of the Tri-State Region 8/67 (Box 22, Folder 23)
  - Tri-State Railroad Suburban Equipment Status Report 5/63 (Box 22, Folder 24)
  - Rationalization of Procedures for Highway Cost Allocation 10/18/90 (Box 22, Folder 25)
  - Rationalization of Procedures for Highway Cost Allocation Studies Executive Summary 10/90 (Box 22, Folder 26)
  - Tri - State Transportation Commission Regional Development Alternates 3/67 (Box 22, Folder 27)
  - Moving America: Building the National Transportation Policy 7/89 (Box 22, Folder 28)
  - Regional Development Guide: Goals and Plan for the Tri-State Region 7 and 10/68 (Box 22, Folder 29)
  - Tri-State Transportation Regional Highways Status Report 11/62 (Box 22, Folder 30)
  - Regional Forecast 1985; The Future Size and Needs of the Tri-State Region 12/67 (Box 22, Folder 31)
  - A Report on Conversion of Tri-State Operations from "Committee to Commission" 7/19/65 (Box 22, Folder 32)
  - Road Gang 50th Anniversary Luncheon [brochure] 6/25/92 (Box 22, Folder 33)
  - A Report on Estimating Highway Needs in Urban Areas 4/65 (Box 22, Folder 34)
  - Resource Book on Federal-Aid Highway Program 9/71 (Box 22, Folder 35)
  - Specifications for a New Electronic Data Processing System [Tri-State Transportation Commission] 4/66 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Snapshot Report of Journey to Work Data - Draft 7/24/92 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - "Shaping the Future", FWHA Tri - Regional Engineers Conference 10/26-30/92 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Stewardship Report on Administration of the Federal-Aid Highway Program 1972 5/72 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Streets and Highways: A Regional Report [Tri-State Transportation Commission] 1/68 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Road Work A New Highway Policy 10/68 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - A Statement of National Transportation Policy 9/17/75 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - A Statement of National Transportation Policy 12/76 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Station Fare Collection Kew Gardens - Forest Hills Queens County, New York 7/1/64 - 6/30/65 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - the Nation's Public Works:Report on Highways, Streets, Roads and Bridges 5/87 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Suburban railroad Equipment Status, 1966 Supplement 9/67 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Suburban Railroad Passengers in the Tri-State Region 8/66 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Suburban Service Adjustment Experiment Harlem Division New York Central Railroad 6/65 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Suburban Service Adjustment Experiment Final Report 11/67 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Summary of Travel Trends: 1990 Nationwide Personal Transportation Survey 3/92 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - The Surface Transportation Assistance Act of 1978 (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Tri-State Transportation Committee Technical Bulletin 1.1 3/65 (Box 23, Folder 17)
    Home Interview Survey Sample Design, Production Control of Home Interview Survey, Preliminary Trip Generation Results, Preliminary Estimate of Rail Car Volume and Flow in the Tri-State Region, Domestic Intercity Freight, Manhattan Cordon Crossings
  - Tri-State Transportation Committee Technical Bulletin 1.2 5/65 (Box 23, Folder 18)
    Aerial and Line Maps for Tri-State, Technical Auditing of Home Interview Survey, Population Density - 1960, Employment By Industry in the Tri-State Region, The Tri-State Region Freight Flows
  - Tri-State Transportation Committee Technical Bulletin 1.3 6/65 (Box 23, Folder 19)
    Field Operations of the Home Interview Survey, Geographic Coding of the Travel Surveys, Committed Freeway Mileages in 20 Cities, Use of the Abacus in Urban Transportation Planning
  - Tri-State Transportation Committee Technical Bulletin 1.4 7/65 (Box 23, Folder 20)
    Census Tract Area Measurement By template, What is Software, Financing Tri-State Operations, Transportation Through Cooperation, Testing the Feasibility of a Secaucus Transfer Station, A Beginner's Lexicon of Tri-State Language
  - Tri-State Transportation Committee Technical Bulletin 1.5 9/65 (Box 23, Folder 21)
    London Transport Conditions in 1964, Development of the Highway System in the Tri-State Region, Passenger Trends on the New Jersey Suburban Railroads 1961-1964, Landmarks in Planning the Tri-State Region, Quality Control of Coding
  - Tri-State Transportation Committee Technical Bulletin 1.6 10/65 (Box 23, Folder 22)
    Some of the More Important Trends in the Development of London Transport,Cost of Producing Standard Tri-State Publications, Some Results of the Study of Quantified Regional Development Alternatives, Building Newark Coding Guide, Delineation of the Tri-State Cordon Line
  - Tri-State Transportation Committee Technical Bulletin 1.7 11/65 (Box 23, Folder 23)
    Direct Traffic Assignment: An Antiquarian Addendum, Home Interview Survey Completeness Checking Procedures, Developing the Minimum Comparability Data File, Man Triumphant? Extracts From a Prologue
  - Tri-State Transportation Committee Technical Bulletin 1.8 12/65 (Box 23, Folder 24)
    Job Control in Data Processing; Regional Bus Equipment Inventory; Direct Expenditures by Households for Transportation; Trends in Tractor - Semitrailer Traffic
  - Tri-State Transportation Committee Technical Bulletin 2.1 2/66 (Box 23, Folder 25)
    A Region on the Move: Travel Choices Depend on Destinations; We File It -- And Don't Forget It; An Approach to Maximizing Toll Revenues; Toronto: Rapid Transit's Romance with the Automobile
  - Tri-State Transportation Committee Technical Bulletin 2.2 4/66 (Box 23, Folder 26)
    Software Revisited; Expanding the Home Survey Interview Survey; Blocks Aren't Only for Child's Play
  - Tri-State Transportation Committee Technical Bulletin 2.3 6/66 (Box 23, Folder 27)
    A Profile of Land Planning The Traffic Volume Estimating Techniques, Coding the Truck - Taxi Survey
  - Tri-State Transportation Committee Technical Bulletin 2.4 8/66 (Box 23, Folder 28)
    Transit Trends
  - Tri-State Transportation Committee Technical Bulletin 2.6 12/66 (Box 23, Folder 29)
    Vacancy Rates in the Tri-State Area; How Many Will take Their Cars? Highway Speeds-1; Procedure used in Expanding the Truck Survey
  - Tri-State Transportation Committee Technical Bulletin 3.2 6/67 (Box 23, Folder 30)
    Home Interview Survey Validation - 1; Inside 505 - 501 [Grid coordinates]
  - Tri-State Transportation Committee Technical Bulletin 3. 3 10/67 (Box 23, Folder 31)
    Home Interview Survey; Validation: Suburban Railroads, Urban Rapid Transit, Screen line Checks; The Form of the Urban Region
  - Tri-State Transportation Committee Technical Bulletin 4.1 2/68 (Box 23, Folder 32)
    The Social-Economic Future of the Tri-State Region
  - Tri-State Transportation Committee Technical Bulletin 4.2 3/68 (Box 23, Folder 33)
    The Region's Unique Rapid -Transit System - In Newark
  - Tri-State Transportation Committee Technical Bulletin 4.3 4/68 (Box 23, Folder 34)
    Findings of the Taxi Survey
  - Tri-State Transportation Committee Technical Bulletin (Box 23, Folder 35)
    the Region's Bus Network: Huge, Complex and Varied
  - Test of Gas Turbine Rail Car 1/69 (Box 23, Folder 36)
  - Trans-Hudson Rail Service to Penn station 11/65 (Box 23, Folder 37)
  - Regional Profile: Transit Strike Highlights 1/67 (Box 23, Folder 38)
  - Transportation and Air Quality [Federal Highway Admin] 8/92 (Box 23, Folder 39)
  - Recommendations for Transportation in the National Capital Region 11/1/62 (Box 23, Folder 40)
  - Travel Behavior Issues in the 90's 7/92 (Box 23, Folder 41)
  - Travel Time Budgets and Mobility in Urban Areas 5/74 (Box 23, Folder 42)
  - Tri-state Inventory of Highway Facilities Procedure Manual guide and Coding Guide 1/63 (Box 23, Folder 43)
  - Tri-State Home Interview Survey, Editing Manual 4/64 (Box 23, Folder 44)
  - Tri-State Transportation 1985, an Interim Plan 5/66 (Box 23, Folder 45)
  - Tri-State Truck - Taxi Field Operations Report 8/65 (Box 23, Folder 46)
  - Truck - Taxi Survey Interviewing Procedure Manual 11/64 (Box 23, Folder 47)
  - Tri-State Truck Taxi Survey, Production Control Procedure Manual 8/68 (Box 23, Folder 48)
  - Urban Transportation Planning in the United States, A Historical Overview 2/86 (Box 23, Folder 49)
  - Traffic Engineering [a periodical] 5/60 (Box 23, Folder 50)
    Theoretical Traffic Volume and Timing Studies; Chicago Plans Its Future; The Use of Electronic Computers
  - Traffic Engineering [periodical] 7/60 (Box 23, Folder 51)
    Program 30th Annual Meeting, ITE; New Horizons for Transit in Metropolitan Chicago,The Problem of the Amber Signal Light in Traffic Flow; Traffic Assignment to Street and Freeway Systems; Building a Second United States
  - Victory 1989; Where we are, Where we're going, How we're going to get there 1989 (Box 23, Folder 52)
  - The WASHO Road Test 1955 (Box 23, Folder 53)
    Western Association of State Highway Officials Road Test data analyses and findings
  - Waterborne Freight of the Tri-State Region 3/67 (Box 23, Folder 54)
  - Urban Freeway Development in Twenty Major Cities 8/64 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - AASHTO Seminar 9/22-23/87 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    History of American Interstate Highway System
  - Alternate Federal Roles for Analysis and Assessment in the Consensus-building Process for Transportation 2020 5/88 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - America's Highway Program 1/16/88 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Analysis and Adaptation of the Brake Masters Emergency Break System 11/90 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - A Brief Survey of International Transportation and Highway Related Data Sources 12/20/90 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Bonded Debt in Virginia: Historical Overview and Future Approaches 3/22/86 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Can We Drive Our Cars and Still Have Clean Air? 7/14/89 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Charting Future Highway Transportation 1/12/88 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - The Commercial Driver's License Information System (CDLIS) 11/88 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Components of Urban Transportation 3/24/88 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Counterrevolution 9/2/89 (Box 25, Folder 11)
    Discusses Investment Deficit in Public Works
  - Critique of New directions for the Nation's Public Works, A Congressional Budget Office Report 1988 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Deficit Figuring Doesn't Add Up 2/89 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Economic Growth and Vitality: The Role of Public Infrastructure in the 21st Century 6/22-24/88 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Europes Railway of the 90's 5/90 (Box 25, Folder 15)
    United Nations White Paper
  - Estimating Highway Needs for the 2020 Consensus Transportation Program (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Evaluation of the Washington Office Staffing needs of the Bureau of Motor Carrier Safety 12/10/74 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Exploring the Methodology for Evaluating the Impacts of transportation on Economic Development 12/7/88 (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - Forecast of Highway Trust Fund Revenues to 2005 3/1/89 (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - Federal Aid Funding Scenarios [FY 91 - 95] 1989 (Box 25, Folder 20)